<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><!-- Created from PDF via Acrobat SaveAsXML --><!-- Mapping Table version: 28-February-2003 --><TaggedPDF-doc><?xpacket begin='﻿' id='W5M0MpCehiHzreSzNTczkc9d'?><?xpacket begin="﻿" id="W5M0MpCehiHzreSzNTczkc9d"?>
<x:xmpmeta xmlns:x="adobe:ns:meta/" x:xmptk="Adobe XMP Core 5.6-c017 91.164374, 2020/03/05-20:41:30        ">
   <rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">
      <rdf:Description rdf:about=""
            xmlns:xmpMM="http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/mm/"
            xmlns:xmp="http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/"
            xmlns:pdf="http://ns.adobe.com/pdf/1.3/"
            xmlns:pdfx="http://ns.adobe.com/pdfx/1.3/"
            xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
         <xmpMM:InstanceID>uuid:08c04871-3f9d-3047-9e9d-1663698d6121</xmpMM:InstanceID>
         <xmpMM:DocumentID>uuid:E6CD1E53-EE84-B1A0-038F-4230F16E7ACC</xmpMM:DocumentID>
         <xmp:CreateDate>2020-05-21T22:20:23-04:00</xmp:CreateDate>
         <xmp:ModifyDate>2020-05-21T22:20:23-04:00</xmp:ModifyDate>
         <xmp:CreatorTool>Serif Affinity Publisher (Mar 31 2020)</xmp:CreatorTool>
         <xmp:MetadataDate>2020-05-21T22:20:23-04:00</xmp:MetadataDate>
         <pdf:Producer>PDFlib+PDI 9.1.2p1-i (OS X/macOS)</pdf:Producer>
         <pdfx:trapped>false</pdfx:trapped>
         <dc:format>xml</dc:format>
         <dc:title>
            <rdf:Alt>
               <rdf:li xml:lang="x-default">KM_Branded</rdf:li>
            </rdf:Alt>
         </dc:title>
      </rdf:Description>
   </rdf:RDF>
</x:xmpmeta>
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                           
<?xpacket end="w"?><?xpacket end='r'?><Part><H1>Kaska Miskolczi </H1><Sect><H1>Unicorn Designer & Developer </H1><Sect><P><Link>iamkaska.com </Link></P><P><Link>calendly.com/batmanwgd </Link><Link>kmiskolczi@outlook.hu </Link></P><P>“Don’t be wise in words, be wise in deeds” </P><Figure><ImageData src="images/KM_Branded-NP to Word_img_0.jpg"/></Figure></Sect></Sect><Sect><H1>CV. +1 (208) 789-0671 </H1><P>LANGUAGES SKILLS </P><Sect><P>Arch. Diagrams. Agile Collaboration. Bug Whispering. CI/CD Pipelines. DevOps SME. SAAS & IAAS. eCommerce. Headless CMS/ LMS. App Design & Dev. Web Design & Dev. System Automation. Platform Configs. Embedded Systems. Microservices Eng. Cyber Security. </P><P>Bash/Zsh/Ksh C/C++ HTML/CSS/jQuery. Vanilla JavaScript. TypeScript. React/AngularJS. D3 & Tableau. Drupal &gt;=7. Sitecore. Docker. Terraform. TravisCI/Jenkins. AWS/Azure/IBM. HashiVault. </P><P>Summary & Education </P></Sect></Sect><Sect><Sect><H1>Devising creative solutions to complex problems is my shtick. </H1><P>My blend of artistic insight, critical thinking, and technical prowess, enables me to create engaging media experiences, while solving real-world complex problems for you and your clients. </P><P>Over the course of your search for a new team member, I doubt you’ll find another candidate as passionate about designing sustainable software. </P><P>Should you wish to connect after reviewing my resume, please do not hesitate to reach out. </P><P>Üdözlettel, </P><Figure><ImageData src="images/KM_Branded-NP to Word_img_1.jpg"/></Figure><Sect><H2>EDUCATION </H2><P>Continued Education </P><P>Self-Paced, Life </P><P>Keeping up with libraries via documentation, Online & Local Edu guides course certificates, local colleges, etc </P><P>Florida Gulf Coast University 2009 -2014 </P><P>Philosophy and Artificial Intelligence, where my Bachelor of Arts </P><P>research & experience focused on the philosophy of learning/intelligence. </P></Sect></Sect><Sect><Sect><H1>Professional Experiences </H1></Sect><P>Senior Software Architect | Miskolczi Software Consulting December 2015 -Present (Consulting to avoid corp. conflict of interests) </P><P>Working with Clients to design & develop data visualization/administration portals, logistics and supply chain software, cloud integration APIs, and automation structures to assist in the creative and interactive process sequences revolving around the design, development and deployment of cloud-based software, services and similar end-point/transactional technologies. </P><L><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Worked with clients like Cox Automotive to create and deploy automotive shoppingapplications in JavaScript and C++, utilizing Node and ReactJS frameworks as well. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Managed infrastructure upgrades, analysis and resolution of end user software utilized inpublic, private and gov. sector applications with clients like Boeing and AutoDesk. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Developing kernel kexts for Healthcare hardware & legacy 3rd party systems </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Responsible for US-CERT CVE findings on behalf of clients like ADP Corp. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Utilizing React, Vue, Ionic, Angular & Node JavaScript libraries to create admin portals withregards to business data analysis, and e-commerce platform tracking engagement. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Translating static software designs into functional prototypes with Vanilla JavaScript,TypeScript, HTML/CSS/jQuery and ReactJS </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Creating Docker & Ansible server images for IAAS, microprocessors & data centers for partners </LBody></LI></L><P>Senior Cloud Security & Design Architect | RelayHealth July 2018 -November 2018 </P><P>Major healthcare client consulting contract, created with the intention of helping assist RelayHealth into their migration off-prem legacy HPE non-stop build, to a hybrid MS Azure and AWS cloud environment, with automation of deployments and continuous integration in mind. </P><L><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Designed and implemented system security and data assurance, and enterprise processes,with best practices tailored for healthcare requirements via HIPPA and Gov.CMS. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Wrote and maintained custom scripts to increase system efficiency and performance time,during installations, configurations of operating systems, for an SLA of 99.9999997% </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Implemented network security equipment, including firewalls, two-factor authentication,and antivirus software for networks supporting over 2.5 million users. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Prepared, all documentation and continued grant proposals to support Azure and OpenStackenvironments, implemented with a front-end design for level II tech implementation. </LBody></LI></L><P>Senior User Interface Developer | Booz Allen Hamilton November 2017 -July 2018 (Only left to gain RelayHealth as client, per conflict of interest) </P><P>Started off as a user interface developer with CDC and ArcGIS contracts, who would be able to traverse both design and development to create data analysis dashboards for international datasetsintoD3,GraphQLandJSapplications,primarilyinthegovernmentsector. Afteracouple months of creating development workflows with CI/CD pipelines for our micro-embedded systems, I successfully hacked into the Department of Homeland Security’s DNSSEC and government-wide service platform, landing me a role more specified in cyber security for their micro-services and cloud containers. </P><P>• Maintained strict budgetary and scheduling guidelines to satisfy clients with high-quality,targeted designs with on-shore and off-shore development teams... </P><P><Link>GitHub: @batmanwgd </Link><Link>https://linkedin.com/in/batmanwgd </Link></P><P>Continued from previous page... </P><L><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Designed and executed security measures such as firewalls, MFA, block-chain encryption,and SEIM logging with scripted alerts. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Planned and engineered RESTful web services, consuming Tableau outputs into JSON anddesigned with D3JS, to manipulate dynamic datasets for CDC's and ArcGIS datasets. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Conceived and built optimized mobile and web applications in HTML, CSS, PHP, .NET, C# with Razor, vanilla JavaScript, Angular and NodeJS. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Conceived and built optimized mobile and web applications in HTML, CSS, PHP, .NET, C# with Razor, vanilla JavaScript, Angular and NodeJS. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Conceived and built optimized mobile and web applications in HTML, CSS, PHP, .NET, C# with Razor, vanilla JavaScript, Angular and NodeJS. </LBody></LI></L><P>Software Developer | FierceMarkets February 2017 -November 2017 </P><P>BigData, high performant and largely scalable marketing and engagement platform provider contract, wherein I was hired to perform recursive testing, debugging, automation of their continuous deployment model and create a headless Drupal CMS based publishing environment from wireframe to deployment in stage before off-shore team takes to production. </P><L><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Collaborated with developers and performance engineers to enhance supportability andidentify performance bottlenecks, throughout all stages of our development lifecycle. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Revised, modularized and updated old code bases to modern development standards,reducing operating costs 36%. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Led group of 15 engineers in design and development of headless CMS of Drupal via BashScripting, Drush, and AWS solutions. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features andcorrecting code. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Performed regression, unit-blocked and system-level testing to verify software quality andfunction prior to release. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Compiled specifications, dev. methods and other scripting modifiers for headlessCMS projectinto technical manuals for team. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Interfaced between high-value customers and junior developers, encouraging use of clientfeedback in software updates. </LBody></LI></L><P>Webmaster & 2D/3D Animator | Florida SouthWestern State College April 2014 -November 2016 (Concurrent with 1st major side-contract in Idaho) </P><P>Webmaster for all four college campuses, post transitional name-change from Edison State College and major Presidential scandal. Rehabilitated community image with re-designed branding & marketing strategy/assets. Developed 3D campus mapping software with 2D drone tracking for new sports arena games. Finished tenure with ADA compliance regulation automation platform, which I developed while managing two junior developers in a combination of a headless code-igniter CMS base, cakePHP blend with vanilla JavaScript, Puppet, C++, etc. </P><L><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Gathered and synthesized business requirements, as team representative in executivemeetings, discussing defining and translating user requirements into project designs andimplementation plans, exceeding aggressive deadlines. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Built user interface, data visualizations and designed to eliminate bugs and improve overalluser experience, resulting in 27% increase of enrollment and SEO/SEM click-through rates. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Spearheaded and implemented use of Git and Mercurial version control across all fourcampuses for design and development. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Created powerful headless Content Management System built with HTML, CSS, PHP, vanillaJavaScript, C++, MySQL, Oracle Cloud, AWS, Puppet, and OpenStack solutions, to serve asinterface for client. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Automated consumption of Oracle and SAP data outputs, by custom built RESTful and SOAPmicro-services to manipulate dynamic datasets with multiple entry and touch points. </LBody></LI></L><P><Link>GitHub: @batmanwgd </Link><Link>https://linkedin.com/in/batmanwgd </Link></P><P>Sitecore Webmaster | Abbey Carpet & Floor December 2013 -November 2014 </P><P>Created majorheadlessCMSwithSitecore .NET frameworkas base and e-commerceplatform for all 2000+ retail partners across the continental USA. Headless CMS platform created, still in use today across both corporate and individual franchise retail locations. </P><L><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Liaised with customers to determine pre-development design specifications, includingfinished design parameters, implementation deliverables and to meet strict deadlines. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Built user interface, data visualizations and designed overall user experience, resulting in67% increase in sales and100% improvement in ADA/WCAG compliance. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Delivered drastic improvements to new headless CMS framework, developed off a Sitecoredistr., still in use today, leading to 97% efficiency boost, with emphasis on realtime APIintegrations with other big-box retailers across the continental USA. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Wrote server-side and client-side code for C# and .NET and .NET Core projects using BashScripting, PHP, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, specifically with Angular and Node frameworks. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Created detailed performance KPIs and analytical reports on client website strategies, honinguser demographics and statistics using Google Analytics and custom vanilla JavaScriptautomation. </LBody></LI></L><P>Aircraft Weight & Balance Alg. Engineer | United Parcel Service September 2012 -February 2014 (Left to finish remaining school term, per 3am start time) </P><P>Webmaster for all four college campuses, post transitional name-change from Edison State College and major Presidential scandal. Rehabilitated community image with re-designed branding & marketing strategy/assets. Developed 3D campus mapping software with 2D drone tracking for new sports arena games. Finished tenure with ADA compliance regulation automation platform, which I developed while managing two junior developers in a combination of a headless code-igniter CMS base, cakePHP blend with vanilla JavaScript, Puppet, C++, etc. </P><L><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Identified issues with software components and isolated regulation faults prior toimplementing corrective actions. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Interpreted aircraft specifications, diagrams and blueprints and compared information tocompleted work verify quality and assess vehicle integrity. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Assisted dismantling and repairing of reconditioned aircraft structural parts and hangarequipment to repair malfunctions and enhance functionality, performance and durability. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Adhered to strict safety procedures and protocols when creating automated logarithmicfunctions via Binary, ASM, C/C++ libraries, protecting both flight personnel and softwareequipment. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Cultivated vast knowledge of aircraft systems by attending training workshops, enhancingfunctionality of systems, automating the checkout control features of our Boeing cargoaircraft and implementation of expertise in routine work and special projects. </LBody></LI><LI><Lbl>• </Lbl><LBody>Saved USP over $2 million by implementing cost-saving initiatives that addressed longstanding problems related to our incremental weight and balance control system. </LBody></LI></L><P>Check me out on LinkedIn | <Link>linkedin.com/in/batmanwgd </Link>For More information on other roles and certificates </P><P>Schedule an Appointment with Me | <Link>calendly.com/batmanwgd </Link>In order to get on my calendar for calls, meetings or anything else :) </P><P><Link>GitHub: @batmanwgd </Link><Link>https://linkedin.com/in/batmanwgd </Link></P></Sect><Sect><H1>Professional Experiences </H1></Sect></Sect></Part><Part><H1>Kaska Miskolczi </H1><Sect><H1>Unicorn Designer & Developer </H1><P>“A little bit of light, pushes out a lot of darkness.” </P></Sect></Part><Part><H1>Üdvözlettel. </H1><Sect><Sect><H1>Taking Clients. </H1><P>Mondays through Thursdays8:30am to 4:00pm Atlanta, Georgia </P><P>Primarily looking for full-time roles with a collaborative team & longevity. </P><P><Link>@batmanwgd </Link><Link>kmiskolczi@outlook.hu </Link></P></Sect></Sect><Sect><Sect><H1>Design Portfolio. </H1><P><Link>https://kaska.myportfolio.com </Link></P></Sect><P><Link>iamkaska.com </Link></P><P>:) </P><Sect><Figure><ImageData src="images/KM_Branded-NP to Word_img_2.jpg"/>HireMe.:)</Figure></Sect><P>+1 (208) 789-0671 </P></Sect></Part></TaggedPDF-doc>